locateadoc.com 2012-10-14

# Privacy Notice

Last Updated: Nov 21, 2011

LocateADoc.com regards your privacy seriously. Our Privacy Policy was developed as an extension of our commitment to excellence in customer service. Our policy was designed to be easy to read and understand what we do with your information and the measures we take to ensure its security. If you have any questions after reading this, please contact us through our feedback form. **By visiting LocateADoc.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.**

LocateADoc, LLC has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact our Client Services Specialists through our feedback form, or by phone at (407)-206-0700 Mon-Friday 9AM-5PM EST, or by postal mail at 1080 Woodcock Road, Orlando, FL, 32803. If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint). 

## What Information About its Visitors Does LocateADoc.com Gather?

  *  **Information You Give Us**

This refers to any active information you choose to provide in order to gain the full use of the website (contact a doctor) or through our contact forms. Generally, we require you to disclose your first and last name, address, city, state, zip, country, phone number and email address. Optional information disclosed includes: company name, province, fax number and any medical/personal information that will help the doctor. If you choose to post information through our website(s) or maintain email, postal mail or telephone contact with us, we may retain such information also. 

  * **Automatic Information from Cookies**

For account management and anti-fraudulent purposes, LocateADoc.com uses cookies to collect information on how our site is used. Automatic Information gathered may included the date and time of visits, the site pages viewed, time spent at our site, the sites visited just before and just after our site. The date is used to simplify subsequent interactions with that site by the same user or to use the information to streamline the user's transaction on related web pages. This makes its easier for a user to move from site to site and to complete transactions over the internet. Cookies should make your online experience easier and more personalized. If you do not wish to transmit cookie information about yourself, please consult the Help section of your web browser to correctly do so. 

We do link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. 

If you choose to refuse cookies, then certain featured of LocateADoc.com will not work for you. For example, we cannot save you time by prefilling contact forms you are using to contact doctors. We also won't be able to determine what stage in the process of learning about your procedure or surgery you are, or remember in what part of the country you are looking for a doctor in, and because of this we won't be able to customize the content on our site to your needs. 

Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. 

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by LocateADoc, LLC only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

## Does LocateADoc.com Share the Information it Receives?

Unless it is necessary in order to provide you with the service you requested we will not disclose your personal identifying information to any third party. A limited number of LocateADoc.com employees, such as customer service representatives, and IT personnel, may have limited access to personal identifying information maintained on our systems, but all are required, by written agreement and subject to substantial penalties, to keep such information strictly confidential and to use it only as a necessary to perform their duties relating to the service that you have requested. LocateADoc.com will never share personal medical or financial information with third parties. 

## How Does LocateADoc.com Use My Information?

Your personal information is used to send your requests for information only to the doctors, dentists, and medical specialists you choose to contact. This information will also be used to prefill forms on the site to make filling forms easier for you, and we will use this data to customize the information on LocateADoc.com to your personal interests. 

We use aggregate (i.e. non-personally identifying) information to determine what our site visitors are viewing on our Web site overall, and analyze the demographics and interests of our users so we can deliver better services to you. 

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

 **Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable):**

We share aggregated demographic information about our user base with our partners and advertisers. This information does not identify individual users. Our advertisers are doctors, dentists and medical specialists who advertise their services on our site. Our partners are companies we work with whom sponsor their services to our advertisers and site visitors. LocateADoc.com's aggregate data is usually shared with these advertisers and partners in a reports for the purpose of describing the sites visitors and usage. 

We do not link aggregate user data with personally identifiable information. 

**Personally identifiable information:**

We Share Personally Identifiable Information with Third Parties 

  * **Service Providers**

We use other third parties to provide patient financing services on our site. When you sign up for patient financing, we will share your name, procedure or surgery or interest, and contact information as necessary for the third party to provide that service. 

  * **Legal Disclaimer**

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site. 

We may disclose anonymous information about user habits, characteristics and user patterns, based on aggregate user statistics to advertisers on our site to Advertisers or other third parties. We may be required by a law or government agency to disclose both active and passive information you have provided us. In the event that LocateADoc.com is sold to a successor company, then all collected information may be transferred to the acquiring / successor company, and that company may publish a new privacy policy. 

  * **Business Transitions**

In the event LocateADoc, LLC goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information. 

## Advertising

Locate A Doc uses technology provided by a third-party to serve ads when you visit this Web site. This technology may use information about your visit to this Web site in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. We customize the advertisements that you see based upon: (i) the information that you knowingly provide; (ii) geographic location which we determine through your IP address; (iii) data we receive from third parties and (iv) your behavior on this Web site or other sites. In the course of serving advertisements to this Web site, such third-party advertising technology may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used to target ads to you, please visit <http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/opting_out.aspx>. In addition, you have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying the settings in your browser. 

Locate A Doc may also use a third party ad network provider, Collective, to help present advertisements on this Web site. Third party network advertisers, along with other advertisers and sponsors on the Web site, may use cookies, web beacons (also called single pixel gifs or action tags) or similar technologies (and, in the case of cookies, access them on your computer if you choose to have cookies enabled in your browser), (i) to serve you advertisements tailored to interests you have shown by browsing on this and other sites you have visited, (ii) to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before, (iii) to avoid sending you duplicated advertisements and (iv) to understand the usage patterns of people who see advertisements. In doing so, the provider collects non-personal data such as your browser type, your operating system, Web pages visited, time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed and other clickstream data. Ad networks may connect information about your visit on our Web site with information about your visit on other sites and show you advertising based on this combined information. The advertisement may appear when you are visiting a different section of this Web site or any other sites on the Internet if such other sites also have a relationship with our ad network provider. The use of third party cookies, web beacons and similar technologies by these ad network providers is governed by each third party's specific privacy policy, not this one. Please visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp> to learn more about the information collection practices and if you wish to "opt-out" of participating in advertising programs conducted by Collective and third party ad network providers. 

We partner with a limited number of behavioral advertising companies to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our websites. Behavioral advertising companies may use cookies to collect non-personally identifiable information [what your search for] during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you. To learn more about this 'behavioral advertising' practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymous information, you can visit the Network Advertising initiative's opt out: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. 

## How Secure is my Personal Information?

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). To learn more about SSL, follow this link <http://www.verisign.com/ssl-certificate/>. 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

Your postings on this site and other communications you may have with us via email or postal mail may not be secure unless we advise you that security measures are in place prior to your sending information. 

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us through our feedback form. 

## Data Retention

We will retain your information for as long as needed to provide you services. We will also retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. If you wish to request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us. 

## User Age Requirement

No person under 13 should disclose information on this site. If we learn that we inadvertently have collected personal identifying information from a child under the age of 13, we will promptly delete that data from our systems and databases. 

## Links to Other Websites

We have links to other websites through our site. When you do so you are doing so subject to their policies regarding privacy and data collection and you should read those sites' privacy policies to make sure you agree with them before using or making purchases. 

## Service Providers

We use other third parties to provide online shopping services on our site. When you use these online shopping services, you are doing so subject to their policies regarding privacy and data collection and you should read those sites' privacy policies to make sure you agree with them before using or making purchases. 

## Co-branded sites

We have online shopping pages on our site that are co-branded with other third parties. We do not collect any personal information on these pages. We also do not have access to any personal information collected by third parties on these pages. When you visit these co-branded pages, you are doing so subject to the privacy and data collection policies of these third parties, and you should read their privacy policies to make sure you agree with them before doing so. 

## Receiving Products and Services

From time to time, you will receive information pertaining to products and services we think you may be interested in. If you would not like to receive this information or if you wish to cancel a request or update your personal information, please contact through our feedback form. Users and/or clients who no longer wish to receive our electronic newsletter or promotional materials from LocateADoc.com and/or our partners may follow the directions on the received email to unsubscribe. 

## Can I Choose to Not Receive Certain Information and/or Opt-out?

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter, notices, and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by contacting us through our feedback form. 

You may also unsubscribe from our newsletter or announcements by visiting our unsubscribe page here. 

You will be notified when your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party. 

  * **Newsletters**

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe. Please see the "Choice and Opt-out" section above. 

  * **Service-related Announcements**

We will send you service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. 

Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account. 

  * **Customer Service**

Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes. 

  * **Profile**

We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, clear gifs, [and/or third party sources] to create a "profile" of your preferences. We tie your personally identifiable information, and your site usage history, to information in the profile, in order to provide tailored promotions and marketing offers and to improve the content of the site for you. 

We share your profile in aggregate form only. 

  * **Email This Page / Tell-A-Friend About LocateADoc.com**

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, either by emailing them a page from our site, or my using our similar Tell-A-Friend About LocateADoc.com feature, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. LocateADoc, LLC. stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. 

Your friend may contact us through our feedback form to request that we remove this information from our database. 

## Supplementation of Information

In order to provide doctor location or educational services, we may on occasion supplement the personal information you submitted to us with information from third party sources. 

## Changes to Privacy Statement

By using our site, you consent to the collection and use of your information as we have outlined in this privacy statement and to our Conditions of Use. LocateADoc.com may decide to change this privacy statement from time to time. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement 30 days before any new changes go into effect, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. 

## Access to Personally Identifiable Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may deactivate it by contacting our Client Services Specialists through our feedback form, or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. 

LocateADoc.com  
1080 Woodcock Road  
Orlando Fl, 32803
